<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WellnessApp</string>
    <!-- String resources for each challenge title  -->
    <string name="meditate">Meditate</string>
    <string name="yoga">Do Yoga</string>
    <string name="stretch">Stretch</string>
    <string name="cooking">Cook a Meal</string>
    <string name="read_book">Read a Book</string>
    <string name="cardio">Do some Cardio</string>
    <string name="walk">Take a Walk</string>
    <string name="lift">Lift Weights</string>
    <string name="music">Listen to Music</string>
    <string name="podcast">Listen to a Podcast</string>
    <string name="clean">Do some Cleaning</string>
    <string name="call_friend">Call a Friend</string>
    <string name="journal">Journal</string>
    <string name="nap">Take a Nap</string>
    <string name="drink_tea">Drink some Tea</string>
    <string name="dance">Dance</string>
    <string name="drink_water">Drink some Water</string>
    <string name="facial">Get a Facial or Massage</string>
    <string name="hike">Take a Hike</string>
    <string name="read_article">Read an Article</string>
    <string name="watch_tv">Watch your Favorite Show</string>
    <string name="gratitude_list">Make a Gratitude List</string>
    <string name="learn_language">Learn a Language</string>
    <string name="fruits_veggies">Try a new Fruit or Vegetable</string>
    <string name="counseling">Take a Counseling Session</string>
    <string name="thank_someone">Thank a Coworker</string>
    <string name="puzzle">Solve a Puzzle</string>
    <string name="take_class">Take a Class</string>
    <string name="play_game">Play a Game</string>
    <string name="volunteer">Volunteer</string>
    <string name="flowers">Buy Yourself Flowers or a Plant</string>
    <!-- String resources for each challenge description  -->
    <string name="meditate_des">Sign up for your free access to Headspace to take a moment for meditation, a simple yet powerful practice that fosters mental clarity, reduces stress, and promotes overall health.</string>
    <string name="yoga_des">Take 20 minutes to transform your body and mind by taking a yoga class. There may be a class offered by your office.</string>
    <string name="stretch_des">Enhance your flexibility and well-being in just 10 minutes by moving away from your desk and stretching your body.</string>
    <string name="cooking_des">Block off some time in your schedule to indulge in the joy of cooking, turning meal preparation into a delightful activity that nourishes both your body and spirit.</string>
    <string name="read_book_des">Take a rejuvenating break and enhance your well-being by reading a book for 20 minutes to immerse yourself in a world of imagination or gain insights that contribute to your personal growth.</string>
    <string name="cardio_des">Use the gym in your office to dedicate 20 minutes to a cardio exercise to foster a stronger heart, increase your stamina, and a revitalize your energy.</string>
    <string name="walk_des">Integrate a refreshing break into your daily routine by allocating time for a brisk walk, stepping away from your workspace and perhaps taking a stroll around the office to invigorate your body and mind.</string>
    <string name="lift_des">Find a time in your schedule to leave your workspace and visit your office\'s gym to lift weights or 20 minutes at your own pace to enhance your quality of life.</string>
    <string name="music_des">Listen to a few of your favorite songs throughout the day, creating mini getaways that transport you to a place of joy and relaxation with your favorite tunes.</string>
    <string name="podcast_des">Listen to a podcast during one of your daily routines to learn and explore new and engaging topics.</string>
    <string name="clean_des">Turn your cleaning routine into a therapeutic act of self-care, creating a clutter-free space that not only enhances your physical surroundings but also contributes to a clear and revitalized state of mind.</string>
    <string name="call_friend_des">Take a moment out of your day to call a friend to reconnect, share laughter, and strengthen bonds with the warmth of meaningful conversations.</string>
    <string name="journal_des">Carve out moments at the close of each day for introspection, allowing yourself the space to reflect and nurture a deeper connection with your thoughts and experiences</string>
    <string name="nap_des">Boost your energy levels by either choosing a 15-minute rejuvenating nap in your office\'s nap room or prioritizing an earlier bedtime, ensuring a refreshed and invigorated start to your day. Full-time employees have access to Sleepio.</string>
    <string name="drink_tea_des">Pause and recharge by heading to the micro-kitchen, where you can prepare a comforting cup of tea to enjoy a rejuvenating break.</string>
    <string name="dance_des">Immerse yourself in the joy of movement and uplift your spirits by dancing to 3 of your favorite songs.</string>
    <string name="drink_water_des">Visit your office micro-kitchen at least three times today for a refreshing glass of water, promoting optimal hydration and supporting your overall well-being.</string>
    <string name="facial_des">Explore the wellness perks at your office by checking for massage services, or indulge in relaxation by booking a facial to unwind and rejuvenate.</string>
    <string name="hike_des">Embark on a rejuvenating journey by taking a hike around your area, connecting with the beauty of nature and enjoying a refreshing escape from the daily grind.</string>
    <string name="read_article_des">Take a moment to read an interesting article for a brief yet insightful escape into new ideas and perspectives.</string>
    <string name="watch_tv_des">Unwind and treat yourself by watching an episode of your favorite TV show, turning a brief break into a delightful escape</string>
    <string name="gratitude_list_des">Nurture a positive mindset by dedicating a moment to create a gratitude list, acknowledging and appreciating the people, places, and things that bring joy and fulfillment into your life.</string>
    <string name="learn_language_des">Expand your knowledge by learning 10 of your favorite words in a new language today.</string>
    <string name="fruits_veggies_des">Embrace a culinary adventure by trying a new fruit or vegetable, adding a burst of flavor and nutritional variety to your palate.</string>
    <string name="counseling_des">Prioritize your well-being by utilizing one of your free 25/year employee assistance program (EAP) counseling sessions, offering a valuable opportunity to engage with a counselor and foster mental and emotional health</string>
    <string name="thank_someone_des">Boost your positivity and strengthen connections by taking a moment to express gratitude – send a sincere thank you to a coworker for their contribution and support</string>
    <string name="puzzle_des">Engage your mind and unwind simultaneously by solving a puzzle, turning moments of mental challenge into a rewarding and enjoyable exercise for your well-being.</string>
    <string name="take_class_des">Explore personal and professional development opportunities by checking for classes offered in your office, accessing free skills courses on go/grow, or considering personal classes. Don\'t forget to explore the education reimbursement program for potential reimbursement benefits.</string>
    <string name="play_game_des">Relax and recharge by playing a game, turning leisure time into a fun and engaging activity that not only entertains but also rejuvenates your mind.</string>
    <string name="volunteer_des">Make a positive impact on your community and enrich your sense of purpose by utilizing your allocated 20 volunteer hours a year to contribute to a cause or organization that aligns with your values.</string>
    <string name="flowers_des">Pamper yourself, nurture your well-being, and brighten your space by treating yourself to a bouquet of flowers or a vibrant plant.</string>
</resources>